Callum Gill

callumgill99@outlook.com | Mobile: 07729387663 | https://www.linkedin.com/in/callum-gill-6a3b17179/

Portfolio website: https://musing-poincare-55331e.netlify.app

User Profile

I have just completed a three year full time course at Edge Hill university studying web design and development. I have graduated from studies in July 2021 achieving a 2:1 in this degree. During my time at on this course I have been exposed to a range of skills from lots of fields in the web industry. Front end development (HTML, CSS, JS). Backend development (Laravel,MySQL,Firebase). Also testing/UX design. From work experience I have developed many life skills this being teamwork, communication and being able to work under stressful conditions.

Education

2018 - 2021 Edge Hill University

BSc (Hons) Web Design and Development-2:1

- User Design Experience module was based around UX which helped me grasp the idea of the need of user interaction during the product creation to be able to add towards user satisfaction.
- Server & Client-Side Scripting module had soft knowledge of full stack deployment which will help in the process of knowledge in what over people will need to do with my work so I can have better understanding if issues arise.
- Web Application Development module showed non-user testing this helps with testing without user and how to complete this.
- The final project was a creation of a web app which will need HTML, CSS and JS and UX/Design which encompasses most skills needed for front end development and help gain valuable skills. This will also be the same for my portfolio modules without the UX elements.

2015 - 2017 Burnley College, Burnley

BTEC Level 3 Extended Diploma in Software Development

D*D*D

2010-2015 Shuttleworth College

GCSE 9 (4B,5C) including English and Maths

Work Experience

May 2016 - September 2017 McDonalds Burnham Gate, Burnley

Responsibility's

- Being able to work in a busy environment
- Being able to work as part as team to make sure everything runs smoothly
- Checking food stock and then refilling stations so people don't run out of stock which would slow down the whole operation
- Cleaning the work stations throughout the day

September 2015 – April 2016 Fat giraffe, Padiham

Pot wash/Waiter

Interests and Activities

Enjoy creating websites and sharing content for others to see. I also enjoy all kinds of sports I have played for a football team for 6 years while at university highly attending sports events for football and cricket this was not competitive and more aimed for fun but again have to be used to new people and best devise how to use certain people at their strengths.